<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on glowybits</title>
    <link>https://www.glowybits.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on glowybits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jasmin Patry</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 16:45:54 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.glowybits.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Filmic Tonemapping and the Scene-to-Screen Transform</title>
      <link>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2017/02/26/scene_to_screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 16:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2017/02/26/scene_to_screen/</guid>
      <description>Shortly after publishing my last post, I started thinking about the similarity between the scene-to-screen transforms that I showed there, and the shape of the &amp;ldquo;toe&amp;rdquo; of filmic tonemapping operators, and I realized that they&amp;rsquo;re both doing the same thing: compensating for the dim or dark surround of the viewing environment. A filmic tonemapping operator is simulating the response of film that will then be projected in a dark theatre, so it has the &amp;ldquo;scene-to-screen&amp;rdquo; transform already baked in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDR Display Support in Infamous Second Son and Infamous First Light (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2017/01/04/ifl_iss_hdr_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 07:39:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2017/01/04/ifl_iss_hdr_2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Back! (And Happy New Year!) This is the second post of a two-part series discussing the technical aspects of adding HDR support to Infamous Second Son and Infamous First Light. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read it already, Part 1 discusses our HDR tonemapping and color grading solutions, as well as the HDR-friendly render target format we used to help improve performance. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll discuss how we matched the look of the SDR and HDR modes (in the darker parts of the image), a couple more performance optimizations, as well as some issues we ran into when combining HDR and 4K on the PS4 Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDR Display Support in Infamous Second Son and Infamous First Light (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2016/12/21/ifl_iss_hdr_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 23:07:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.glowybits.com/blog/2016/12/21/ifl_iss_hdr_1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Last month, Sucker Punch released patches for both Infamous Second Son and First Light that added HDR and 4K display support. This two-post series will focus on some of the technical aspects of adding HDR support to these games; I&amp;rsquo;ll save a discussion of 4K support for a (possible) separate post. (For a more consumer-oriented description of the features we added with these patches, please see Jason Connell&amp;rsquo;s post on the PlayStation Blog).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
